wow-coupons.com 2018-08-29

# Wow-Coupons - #1 Deals source of Free Online, Printable retail, Grocery store and Restaurant Coupon Codes.

Our Commitment to Privacy

Our privacy policy is an extension of our commitment to providing high quality and value in products and services and to integrity in dealing with our users. This policy is designed to clarify how we collect, use, and protect your personal information and to help you make informed decisions about using our site, products, and services. What Information Do We Collect?When you visit **WOW Coupons** , you may provide us with two types of information: personal information that you choose to disclose ("active information") and information about the ways you use the site, collected invisibly and _anonymously_ as you browse ("passive information").

**No one under 13, please!** No part of this website is 

designed to appeal to children, and no one under 13 

years old should disclose personal information on this site. 

Learn more about protecting children’s privacy online by 

visiting  [ www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy).

Active Information

In order to receive coupons via email, you must disclose the following information: 

  * Your email address 
  * Your first name (so that we can greet you properly; 
  * no need for last names)
  * Your state (to help us find the best deals for you, wherever you may be)

** Passive Information **

Our website uses a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about the ways visitors use the site. Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, pages viewed, length of time spent browsing, and sites visited immediately before and after our site. This passive information is collected on an aggregate basis, without any identification, so that you remain anonymous. If you want to prevent cookies from gathering information about you, you may set your web browser to block them; check the Help section of your browser to learn how to do this.

What’s a Cookie?  
  
Cookies are tiny data files that are stored on your computer to enable websites to identify you and keep track of your preferences. They may be temporary (for one session only) or persistent (permanently stored on your hard disk). Cookies help websites to make your online experience easier and more personalized. How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

Active information helps us administer our business activities, provide customer support and other services, and determine what coupons or deals may be of interest to our users. We may use it to contact you about changes to our site; new services, features, or products; or information that we think will be valuable to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please send us an e-mail at  [ elalpo@runbox.com](mailto:elalpo@runbox.com). 

Passive information enables us to make our site easier to use, faster, and friendlier. We use cookies to gather data about how many people visit our site, when they visit, and how they use our service. We do NOT identify any of this information with your name or e-mail address; it’s strictly anonymous. But it helps us tailor the advertising you see on our site to your interests and viewing habits.

When You Click on Links to Other Sites  
  
You can visit other websites through links on **WOW-Coupons.com**. When you do so, you will be bound by those sites’ policies regarding privacy and terms of use. Especially if you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their policies carefully before making any purchases. ** Sharing Information** ****   
  
We will never sell your personal information or share it with anyone; only employees of **WOW-Coupons.com** and contractors performing a service under our direction will ever see it.

We may, however, inform advertisers about the aggregate habits and characteristics of our visitors, using strictly anonymous statistics that we gather with cookies.  Legal Disclosure  
  
On rare occasions, we may disclose personally identifiable information if compelled by law enforcement or government agency. **How Do We Protect Your Information?**  
  
We use all reasonable means to prevent any unauthorized access to your personal information or accidental loss or destruction of data. Communication with us via e-mail or the US Postal Service may not be secure unless we tell you specifically that security measures are in place before you send information. If you do choose to communicate with us through these means, you assume all risk of doing so. ** You Can See, Change, or Delete Your Information** ****   
  
If you ever want to change your information or remove your name from our mailing list, simply send an email to  [ elalpo@runbox.com](mailto:elalpo@runbox.com). You can also remove your name safely with ConstantContact.com (through our newsletter; on the bottom of newsletter).

_We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion, without notice to you.  
Please check this page from time to time to see any changes_.
